My name is Doreen Goge.
I come from South Africa.
My testimony goes like this: I used to sell sweets because I did not have work.
We suffered because nobody in my family went to school.
Now, the other day...
My neighbour had a television in her house.
So, when I was not selling sweets, I would visit my neighbour and watch Emmanuel TV.
While watching Emmanuel TV, I was shocked to see Prophet T.B. Joshua’s biography
and how he had started The SCOAN.
I saw how after he had built the first church building, it was destroyed by a flood.
I saw how many obstacles he faced while he was building the church.
I saw how much Prophet T.B. Joshua had suffered and how Jesus solved his problems.
That day, I cried; the Holy Spirit touched me that day.
I prayed and asked God to help me the way He had helped the man of God.
I was crying and praying as I went back to my home.
There was no television in my house.
So, I would go to my friend’s house and ask her to please let me watch Emmanuel TV and she did.
One day, while I was watching Emmanuel TV, Prophet T.B. Joshua started praying for the viewers.
I touched the screen of my friend’s television and prayed along with the man of God.
I would cry and pray along with Prophet T.B. Joshua on Emmanuel TV every day.
I am better today because I am no longer crying but then, I cried terribly.
Every time Prophet T.B. Joshua talks, the Holy Spirit is there.
I confirm today that Prophet T.B. Joshua is a man of God who does everything, in Jesus’ name.
Now, I have started afresh.
I have left all my trouble with God.
That time, I did not look at my trouble
but rather, I would pray along with the man of God on Emmanuel TV all the time.
Sometimes, I would not be able to watch Emmanuel TV at my friend’s house
because her child would want to watch another channel.
So, I prayed that the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua should give me the power to pray every day in my house.
People of God, many things will happen in your life
if you listen very well to what Prophet T.B. Joshua says all the time.
I used to be an activist for my political party but I was never nominated for any position.
I did not understand it.
Only after I prayed along with Prophet T.B. Joshua daily, did people start recognising me.
They no longer saw me as a woman who was suffering but as a strong woman
because of the strength that the God of Prophet T.B. Joshua gave me.
I told everybody that God is the answer.
One day, people of God, they told me that there was a position open
and that I had been nominated to be a Councillor in my political party.
They nominated my name because of the power of God in my life through the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
I couldn’t believe that I was nominated to be a Councillor.
Mrs Doreen Goge
Emmanuel TV Testimony
At the time they nominated me, I couldn’t speak English but now, I can.
Put your hands together for Jesus!
Mrs Doreen Goge
Emmanuel TV Testimony
Mumma says, then she couldn't speak English but now she is better, she can express herself clearly.
Mrs Doreen Goge
Emmanuel TV Testimony
After I started working in the government as a Councillor,
they decided that all the Councillors in the country who did not go to school should go back.
I started at level one and passed because I prayed everyday with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Mrs Doreen Goge
Emmanuel TV Testimony
I graduated.
Here you can see me in my graduation gown.
Mrs Doreen Goge
Emmanuel TV Testimony
It was the first time I had taken a step to graduate.
I am very happy.
Everybody should please clap their hands and celebrate with me.
Mrs Doreen Goge
Emmanuel TV Testimony
It' OK.
You work "nice" for the people; me, I am doing my best but I am an "old school".
After graduating, I build a house.
Before, I had no money and I was selling sweets.
Now, for the first time, I can go to the bank to draw money.
Mrs Doreen Goge
Emmanuel TV Testimony
God used Prophet T.B. Joshua to bless me more and more.
When I started receiving my salary, I opened a bank account which I did not have before.
I could withdraw 10,000 rands at a time – a woman who once sold sweets for a living.
I started saving my money and after one year, I withdrew more than 100,000 rands
with which I built a house.
Mrs Doreen Goge
Emmanuel TV Testimony
This is my house and there are many rooms in my house.
I don’t owe any debts on this house.
I have finished paying for it.
Even my son who was suffering is now staying with me in my home.
The people in my country love me.
I was able to achieve all this because of praying along with Prophet T.B. Joshua on Emmanuel TV.
I was also able to buy a brand new car – the latest model.
I am learning how to drive now.
As you can see on these photos, I don’t stay at home.
Every day, I wake up early to go and see this old grandmother.
This is a picture showing that I work with and help people of different races.
I give charity to old people and I work with people of all ethnic groups in my country.
What I have achieved today is because of Emmanuel TV.
I thank Prophet T.B. Joshua for taking me from a place where my potential was hidden
to a place where people all over the world can recognise me.
Mrs Doreen Goge
Emmanuel TV Testimony
OK.
You should look at life from God’s point of view – as a child of God, you should shine every day.
When you listen to God, He will tell you many things.
As a Councillor, God told me to take my money and use it to solve people’s problems.
If you listen to God, He will give you back to you in abundance.
I want to tell you everyone to look to God, in the name of Jesus.
Listen to Prophet T.B. Joshua.
God speaks to Prophet T.B. Joshua and he in turn, gives the message to people all over the world.
Take it!
Everything you have today is from God.
Therefore, listen to God; don’t listen to all the trouble around you.
There is so much trouble out there; listen to God all the time!
Thank you very much!
Mrs Doreen Goge
Emmanuel TV Testimony
Mumma, what advice would you give to people who are going through the same situation as you were before?
I never turn the television off in my house.
When I go to work, Emmanuel TV is always on in my home.
When I go to work, Emmanuel TV is always on in my home because it is a deterrent to evil.
When I come back from work, I always praise God.
People should pray to God all the time, no matter what because the devil is a liar.
The devil is not a man but a dog.
God is the only God.
Listen to Emmanuel TV and Prophet T.B. Joshua all the time.
The God of Prophet T.B. Joshua is the answer.
Thank you very much.